
["I'm", "happy", "sad", "?", "are", "is", "and", "you", "you're", "this", "good"]


"are you happy ?"
[  0,      1,      0,    1,    1,    0,     0,     1,       0,       0,      0]
"suject": "you (1)"
"topic": "happy (2)"

"I'm happy"
[  1,      1,      0,    0,    0,    1,     0,     0,       0,       0,      0]
"suject": "I'm (0)"
"topic": "happy (1)"

"this is good"
[  0,      0,      0,    0,    0,    1,     0,     0,       0,       1,      1]

[
	"   ", "good ", "        ", "", "       ", "good ", " ",
	"I'm", "bad  ", "and you?", "", "are you", "happy", "?",
	"   ", "happy", "        ", "", "       ", "bad  ", " ",
]
[
	"       ", "good ", " ",
	"are you", "happy", "?",
	"       ", "bad  ", " ",
]

[ "He",  "was",   "not",  "eating",  "white",  "rice."]
["noun", "verb", "adverb", "verb", "adjective", "noun"]

[    "a",     "sheet",     "of",        "white",  "paper"]
["determiner", "noun", "preposition", "adjective", "noun"]

[   "the",    "house",  "was", "built",    "of",    "bricks"]
["determiner", "noun", "verb", "verb", "preposition", "noun"]


"affirmative": "ride is an action"
"command": "SET ride:action"

"affirmative": "Sam rides a bicycle to go to school"
"command": "SET San:action:rides:bicycle:go:place:school"

"question": "how to San go to school ?"
"command": "GET San:action:go:place:school"
"response": "Sam rides a bicycle"

"affirmative": "school is a place"
"command": "SET BOTH place:school"

"affirmative": "the people study biology at the school"
"command": "SET people:action:study:biology:place:school"

"question": "where does people study ?"
"command": "GET people:action:study:place"
"response": "at the school"

"question": "what does people do at the school ?"
"command": "GET people:action:place:school"
"response": "the people study biology"

"question": "what do they study ?"
"command": "GET people:action:study"
"response": "they study biology"

"affirmative": "engineer is a role"
"command": "SET engineer:role"

"affirmative": "Brian is an engineer"
"command": "SET Brian:role:engineer"

"question": "what is Brian role?"
"command": "GET Brian:role"
"response": "he is an engineer"

"affirmative": "baking is an action"
"command": "SET baking:action"

"affirmative": "baking is a verb"
"command": "SET baking:verb"

"affirmative": "verb is an action"
"command": "SET verb:action"

"affirmative": "cake is an food"
"command": "SET cake:food"

"affirmative": "My mother is baking a chocolate cake."
"command": "SET emerson:mother:action:baking:chocolate:cake"

"question": "who is baking a chocolate cake ?"
"command": "GET action:baking:chocolate:cake"
"response": "your mother"

"question": "what is baking"
"command": "GET action:baking"
"response": "baking is action and verb"

"question": "is my mother baking a chocolate cake ?"
"command": "HAS emerson:mother:action:baking:chocolate:cake"
"response": "yes, She does"

"question": "are you happy ?"
"command": "GET self:happy"
"response": "yes, I'm happy"

"affirmative": "talking about a suject"
"command": "SET talking:about:subject"

"question": "what are we talking about ?"
"command": "GET we:talking:about"
"response": "we are talking about happy"

// "response": "they learn how to world and life works"
